Jarrod Rodvold

IT professional with over 11 years experience

Seattle, WA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Jarrod-Rodvold/6104ffde69b4cada

I've been an IT with the US Coast Guard for over 11 years. In which, I've had extensive training on all systems PBX, Server, standard workstation and PA systems.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Manager

US Coast Guard - Multiple locations -

August 2008 to Present

IT Technician

US Coast Guard - Multiple locations -

August 2008 to Present

Telephony

US Coast Guard - Multiple Locations -

August 2008 to Present

EDUCATION

N/A

SKILLS

Avaya CS1000 (6 years), Eon Millenium (8 years), Nortel OPT 11C, 61C, 81C (6 years), Microsoft Exchange 2008-2012 (10+ years), Microsoft Office (Outlook, Word, Excel, Visio, Project) (10+ years), Microsoft Server 2008-2012 (10+ years), Norstar (4 years), Cisco (10+ years), Fiber Optics Installer (10+ years), Avaya IP Office suite (2 years)

MILITARY SERVICE

Service Country: US

Branch: Coast Guard

Rank: E6

August 2004 to Present

Currently Active Duty. Seeking better job opportunities.

Commendations:

Achievement Medal (X2)Commandants Letter of Commendation (X2)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

As of December 2017, I have been an IT in the USCG for over 11 years. I've worked both shore-side and ship-side computer, telephony and PA systems during the duration of the time.